Headmistress Olivia?!
It's been too long, everyone.
The Night Before the Battle
Thank you for your help the other day, Dolan.
Sure.
What are you doing here,
Headmistress Olivia?
I'm an elf born of this village.
I left the forest to live in
the outside world ages ago,
but I rushed here when I heard the news.
Oh, I see.
So you already knew Olivia?
May we proceed now?
We have no intention of waiting out
the three days this Georg laid out.
Tomorrow, as the sun is halfway to its peak,
we will gather our forces
still capable of fighting,
destroy the portal to the demonic realm,
and send them packing from the surface.
They can only stay here because of
the energy the portal provides them.
Right.
If we destroy the portal, they'll
be unable to sustain their presence
or return here afterward.
Then the forest will be able to cleanse itself.
We understand your intentions.
We've spoken to Gio about this,
and we intend to continue fighting with you.
Hm... But we can't ask outsiders
to provide even further aid.
Are you underestimating us...
is what I'd like to say, but you
clearly possess formidable strength.
If anything, we should be bowing our heads
to the ground to ask for your assistance.
Dio, I get that it's pathetic of us,
but we're in a situation where
we need all the help we can get.
You're not wrong.
I agree with Vlaic.
Dolan, Christina, and Celina.
We feel incredibly fortunate
to hear your offer.
Please lend us your strength.
Dio, I promise you that these
three are highly reliable.
I have requested help from
the kingdom, as well.
Oho?
They'll take a little while to arrive,
but they'll provide a way to reclaim
the forest even if we were to lose.
Very well.
Dolan, Celina, and Christina,
we're counting on you.
I can feel their strong desire
to protect their forest.
I want to fulfill that desire
any way I possibly can.
Of course. We'll do everything in our
power to live up to your expectations.
I'll do my best!
We swear to rid the forest of those fiends!
Damn that superhuman girl!
Those detestable fools!
And how dare that surface flower scar me!
You're going too far, Geolude and Raflasia.
These soldiers don't grow
on trees, you know.
Georg, why won't you say
something to stop them?
Let them be.
Their spirits must be raging
before the upcoming battle.
Yes, but so is mine.
That lamia lass may be too young for
her scales to have hardened yet,
but she has potential.
I very much took a liking
to that Dolan guy, too.
I am convinced we can have the kind of
battle I haven't tasted in a long while.
Oh? I'm happy for you.
I thought you were unable to enjoy a fight
outside the celestial and demonic realms.
Take that!
Oh, stop it already!
Dolan...
The combat capabilities, mana, and
fighting spirit he showed in our battle...
There is no mistaking it.
Back when I was part of the
war god Ardes's army...
Stupid fallen gods.
They've created such annoying monsters.
Even we have to gang up on them.
I'm worried about Ardes on the front lines.
We must head there at once.
What?!
I've heard that Goddess Myrale summoned him.
He must be on his way to Ardes.
What's wrong, Georg?
The ancient dragon who once demolished
and massacred the demons,
and made them tremble at the
very mention of his name,
the alpha and the omega...
And he has now become a human?
Either way, it's sure to be a battle
that gets the blood boiling.
Hurry to me.
It has truly been eons since I
have anticipated a battle so.
What do you want so late at night?
I was looking for you.
Why?
I'm not in a very good mood right now.
Who knows what I might do
if you get too close to me.
I just wanted to take care of something
bothering me before tomorrow's battle.
Am I not good enough to fight with you?
Hey! Didn't you hear me tell
you not to get close to me?
I did, which is why I did it with caution.
You're a strange one.
I get that a lot.
So much so that I've gotten used to it.
Your wound hasn't healed.
The ones Raflasia gave you.
You see right through me, huh?
Mind if I take a look?
It's nothing to concern yourself over.
I can't believe you were
walking around in this state.
I'll purify it with some of my life energy.
Please don't resist it.
I'm starting to wonder
if you're really human.
I'd appreciate it if you thought of
me as one, albeit a little unusual.
Were you grieving them?
Raflasia killed some really
beautiful spirits.
None of them deserved to
go out the way they did.
Not one.
That's why I can't stand it.
I have to get revenge for their souls.
And I will.
Will you let me help you with that?
You really are strange...
or "unusual," as you would have it.
Thank you for healing me.
I'm surprised how glad I am that we talked.
Dolan.
I'm back.
You're here too, Fio and Merl.
I brought you some tea.
It's floral tea, with added nectar.
Fio's favorite.
We've started before you.
Here, this is dinner.
Thanks, Celina.
Did you bring this too, Fio?
Yep. Can't have you fighting
on an empty stomach, see.
It's really delicious.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Ah, a very comforting meal.
I could eat this forever.
I'm glad you like it.
Christina practically inhaled
it in no time, too.
That was unbecoming of me.
I'm surprised you can eat so
much and still stay so slim.
I don't gain weight easily.
Plus, I exercise as much as I eat.
Still, you're slim in the waist
and stacked where it counts.
As a fellow lady, I am super envious.
Ugh!
If you ask me, you're both plenty
stacked and have great curves.
Dolan, could you stop
staring for one second?
You're a boy of age,
so I can understand why,
but please pick a better time and place...
Oh, I didn't have any
dirty thoughts in mind.
I was just thinking that Fio
had no need to envy anyone.
Oh, yeah? Well, I guess
I'll leave it at that.
Otherwise, it'll look like
we're bullying you here.
Do you want to bully Dolan?
You're reading too much into it.
Perhaps we should've discussed
this without male presence.
Yeah. Let's continue some other time.
We have an early start tomorrow.
We should turn in for the night.
Yeah.
I'll clean up, Dolan.
Thanks.
Celina.
Dolan...
You couldn't sleep, either?
No, I just...
Yeah, I couldn't sleep,
so I stepped out for some fresh air.
So we had the same thought.
Look. I only found it a while ago,
but it's already my favorite.
I'm sure it'll make you feel better, too.
Your favorite, huh?
This should be good.
It's amazing how beautiful
this elven village is.
The moonlight trickles
gently through the trees.
Only made possible because they've lived
in harmony in nature for millennia.
I can hear clanking in the
distance when I focus.
It's cute.
The smiths must be working all
night to prepare for tomorrow.
They want to help their
friends win the battle.
I-I'm so sorry for
thoughtlessly calling it cute.
No, that was insensitive of me to bring up.
You were right.
This scenery really soothes the soul.
Right?
Celina, people may call me strange,
but I'm not entirely unperceptive.
Huh? Where is this coming from?
I've noticed your anxiety ever since we
came to the village after that battle.
Huh?
I dragged you into this mess despite
knowing you're unsuited to warfare.
That's not it!
This isn't because I'm scared
of fighting or anything, but...
Hm?
I could have killed that demon back then.
All I had to do was squeeze
him tight with Jalaam.
But I couldn't do it.
Even though so many of the
elves and Diadora got hurt,
and even though I know
that demon was a bad guy.
I couldn't bring myself to end his life,
and I froze in place.
I'm a terrible lamia.
I know I have to change, but still...
Yeah, I always thought lamia
were more cold-blooded.
Until I met you, that is.
Huh?
If you were the type of cold-blooded
lamia told of in legend,
I wouldn't have thought of
welcoming you into the village.
You have no need to change.
I prefer you just the way you
are, a kind and gentle soul.
Come on, Dolan...
Here, Celina.
Huh?
Is that... a magic crystal?
Wait, no!
What is it? It has several times
the energy of a magic crystal!
It's my favorite—and its
production method is a secret.
I crafted it hoping that
it would keep you safe.
And it will do just that
in tomorrow's battle.
So trust me, and you'll
have nothing to fear.
Thank you.
Sure.
Ch-Chris?!
You'll catch a cold being
outdoors this late.
Also...
It's unfair that you're leaving
me out of this spectacular view.
Join us.
Let's take it in together.
How I want to protect
this beautiful village.
Right.
Dolan, Christina... I won't waver anymore.
I get it now!
I want to help Gio, Fio, Merl,
and all the other villagers.
That's what I want to do most right now.
So I won't waver this time!
Same here.
I'll cut down evil to help everyone here!
You're so cool, Chris!
Y-You think?
She really must've been stressed out.
Yeah.
Dolan, I have a weird question.
Have you heard the word "superhuman" before?
No, can't say that I have.
No? That's fine. Forget I asked.
Fellow warriors!
You who live with the blessings
of the Forest of Ente!
With the appearance of those
wretched demons in these lands,
many of our brethren have
fallen prey to them
and become part of the forest,
which in turn has been defiled by the enemy
and is screaming out in pain.
I will not forget their lamentation!
I will not forget their hatred!
I will not forget their wrath!
Now is the time to avenge their
deaths and let our righteous rage,
as we bring judgment
down upon those fiends!
Yeah!
Our target, the demonic portal,
has one main gate and three
auxiliary gates surrounding it.
The elven warriors led by me,
the beastkin squad led by Vlaic,
and the arachne squad led by Alsienne
will handle each of those gates.
Captain Gio's squad will be our ranger unit.
The main objective will be to deliver
you to the main gate at full strength.
Elf, beastkin, arachne, spirit,
and all forest dwellers alike
are staking everything on you.
Please, save the Forest of Ente!
There.
The demons are here.
Celina?
Go ahead without me.
I'll help Gio's squad.
What? Why would you go off by yourself?
Dolan, Chris, I'll be fine.
I have nothing holding me back.
Fine. Don't push yourself, Celina.
I won't.
Ready or not, here comes Celina!
Next Episode
This week's lucky item is a bracelet!
Look forward to next time!